Draper Corporation Photographs 6612 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Miscellaneous Hopedale photos, black and white photograph (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Item 2305: Hopedale Town Hall interior, Welcome Home Banquet for World War I Veterans. Copy 4., 1919; black and white photograph (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Item 2305: Hopedale Town Hall interior, Welcome Home Banquet for World War I Veterans. Copy 3., 1919; black and white photograph (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Item 2305: Hopedale Town Hall interior, Welcome Home Banquet for World War I Veterans. Copy 2., 1919; black and white photograph (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Item 2308: Fire Station decorated with flags and bunting, Copy 2., 1919; black and white photograph (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Printed from glass plate negative no.B2308. December 20, 1919. Image depicts a fire station in Hopedale, Massachusetts, a two-story brick building with a tower on the end. Building is lavishly draped in flags and bunting in celebration of the end of World War I. The sign at the center of the building reads, "Our Heros, Welcome Home." Original photograph by the Draper Corporation. 25.25 x 20.25 cm.
- P1135 - photos of pages from a book, black and white photograph (Box 17, Folder 5)
- P1135 - Miscellaneous photos, black and white photograph (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Contact Prints #1158 - 1299 (incomplete), black and white photograph (Box 17, Folder 7)
- P353.22-.50 (incomplete), black and white photograph (Box 17, Folder 8)
- P298.35N, P295.37-.38, P53.25, P1.148, P2393, black and white photograph (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous photos, black and white photograph (Box 17, Folder 10)
- P572 photos, black and white photograph (Box 17, Folder 11)
- SB 1001, 1007, black and white photograph (Box 17, Folder 12)
- 3936, black and white photograph (Box 17, Folder 13)
- 3994, black and white photograph (Box 17, Folder 14)
- B1350-B1378, black and white photograph (Box 17, Folder 15)
- 1380-1415, black and white photograph (Box 18, Folder 1)
- 1416-1459, black and white photograph (Box 18, Folder 2)
- 1460-1505, black and white photograph (Box 18, Folder 3)
- 1506-1580, black and white photograph (Box 18, Folder 4)
- B39-B4019 (incomplete), black and white photograph (Box 18, Folder 5)
- F.P. 43-F.P. 208, black and white photograph (Box 18, Folder 6)
- P261 -- Photographs from Glass-Plate Negatives - Series A10 A297 ---- Film Negatives - Series B39 B549 [contents of a binder], black and white photograph (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Close-up view of battery on Draper Company loom, Model E, with duplex harness. Copy 2., black and white photograph (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Printed from glass plate negative no.A22. 1894-1900. Image depicts a close-up view of the battery on a Draper Company Model E loom with a duplex harness. A battery is a mechanism found on single box automatic looms. The battery holds a plentiful supply of filling bobbins and transfers them, one at a time, to the shuttle as the need arises. The Draper Company, located in Hopedale, Massachusetts, manufactured textile machinery, primarily looms. See Box 1, Folder 2, Item 27 for a view of the entire loom. 25 x 20.25 cm.
- P261 -- Photographs from Glass-Plate Negatives --- Series B550 B1786, black and white photograph (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Information sheets for some of the photos - list received with collection - numbering reflects collection received, black and white photograph (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Model "A" Loom and Little Red Shop, black and white photograph (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Little Red Shop, black and white photograph (Box 19, Folder 4)
    First home of the Draper Corporation
  - Item 2: Front view of Draper Company "X-3" model power loom, black and white photograph (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Front view of Draper Company "A" model cam loom, black and white photograph (Box 19, Folder 4)
- P261 - Oversize negatives -- Glass Plate negatives --- Series A10 A297 --- Film Negatives --- Series B39 B549 --- 7 negatives, black and white photograph (Box 20, Folder 1)